GENEVRA ROSE

858 633 3744 • Irvine, CA • work@gmr.dev

https://gmr.dev

SUMMARY

Hi! I'm Genevra, an experienced Software Engineer. I've been coding since I was a 13, and I know computers inside and out! I'm highly experienced with C#, Unity3D (all facets), Virtual Reality/Augmented Reality stuff, JavaScript (including frameworks such as React.js), HTML5+CSS3, PHP, Python, and some C++. Long hours playing and modding nostalgic games like Pokémon have allowed me to pick up smaller scripting languages, too. I'm also quite agreeable and easy to work with! Please don't hesitate to reach out if you are interested in working with me.

EXPERIENCE

Vocabubot Aug. 2017 – Aug. 2018

https://vocabubot.com

Learned PHP & SQL from scratch in a month to build, launch, and distribute from the ground up a service that does your homework for you. Uses the PayPal payment API in order to process customer payments and maintain relationships. Built in HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, MySQL.

Key Accomplishments:

- Managed customer orders and marketing to reach over 50 customers in the first 2 months of operation alone.
- Created an entirely new niche and product from scratch.
- Managed and created multiple SQL databases for customer data.
- Product is extremely attractive for consumer, translates into 140 hours saved per year with automation.

Stay in the Circle Nov. 2018 - Jan. 2019

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gmr.circle

Built and deployed a mobile app that leverages the Google ecosystem in order to generate revenue.

- Over 50% retention rate in the first week.
- Contacted by and collaborated with Chartboost publishing.
- Unity3D + C#
- Published to both iOS and Android App Stores.

Wall Ball Apr. 2019

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.gmr.wallball

Built and deployed a mobile app that is beautifully designed with extremely efficient, performant code.

- App size less than 40% of its competitor average in that genre.
- Includes no advertisements or annoying popups.
- Slick, responsive design with no lag.

Diamond Dodge Sep. 2019

https://youtu.be/ppWMjS7Unws

Built a simulation for the latest in VR tech that shows common use-cases of most VR game techniques.

- Unity3D + C# released for Oculus Rift, VIVE, and the HTC VIVE PRO.
- Built in crunch time 3 days.
- Keep a diamond away from ships that attempt to blow it up, must move it around in real time.
- Throw fireballs at the ships to explode them.
- Fireballs are affected by Earth's gravity, so player must take that into account.

Pokémon Unity 2018 - 2020

https://github.com/PokemonUnity/PokemonUnity

Run massive community project and maintain community around repository and Discord Server.

Gain over 20 members per month.

- 650+ members to date.
- Largest Pokémon RPG engine repository.
- Over 2000 successful commits over the past 3 years.
- Most Members: Pokémon RPG engine Discord Server.

RuneTale 2016

https://gmr.itch.io/runetale

Fangame based off UNDERTALE, received over 500 downloads in the first month with overwhelming support.

Key Accomplishments:

- Desktop application built in C#.
- Over 500 downloads from various community members.
- Virtually a perfect replication of the UNDERTALE engine.
- Conceived and deployed with a small team of five, managed and led team to successful completion of project.
- Leadership in building game from scratch, used Git to keep track of commits.

Upwork Freelance Work

2019 - Present

Work and communicate with multiple clients, including Cirocco Studios, White Moon Dreams.

- Worked on Asteroid Invaders! https://store.steampowered.com/app/1090340/Asteroid_Invaders/
- Communicated and developed multiple 3d, 2d, and VR games for over 10 different clients.
- Created multiple VR experiences.

Blog

https://gmr.dev/blog

EDUCATION

Saddleback College | Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

2021

JSerra High School

n School 2018

Received honor roll all 4 years.

University of San Diego

- Ethical Hacking Class
- Digital Forensics Class

SKILLS

C# | Unity3D | HTML (5) | CSS (3) | PHP (7) | JavaScript | SQL | Python | Lua | ActionScript3 | C++ (Basic Knowledge)

VR | Microsoft Office | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Illustrator | Adobe Premiere | Adobe After Effects | Adobe Animate (Flash)

Electron

SOCIAL MEDIA

Blog: https://gmr.dev/blog

Website: https://gmr.dev

Twitter: @GMR517

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/genevrarose/